Where will your imagination take you?
Finding Neverland is a drama, fantasy film directed by Marc Forster.
During a writing slump, playwright J.M.
Barrie meets a widow and her four children, all young boys—who soon become an important part
of Barrie’s life and the inspiration that lead him to create his masterpiece.
Sir James Matthew Barrie, played by Johnny Depp.
Sylvia Llewelyn Davies, played by Kate Winslet.
Mrs. Emma du Maurier, played by Julie Christie.
Charles Frohman, played by Dustin Hoffman.
Peter Llewelyn Davies, played by Freddie Highmore.
Mary Ansell Barrie, played by Radha Mitchell.
Finding Neverland is a 2004 biographical fantasy film directed by Marc Forster and written by
David Magee, based on the 1998 play The Man Who Was Peter Pan by Allan Knee.
The film stars Johnny Depp, Kate Winslet, Julie Christie, Radha Mitchell, and
Dustin Hoffman, with Freddie Highmore in a supporting role.
Finding Neverland premiered at the Venice Film Festival on September 4, 2004, and was released in the United
Kingdom on October 29, 2004, and the United States on December 17, 2004 by Miramax Films.
It was a box office success, grossing $116.8 million worldwide.
The film earned seven nominations at the 77th Academy Awards, including Best Picture, Best
Adapted Screenplay, and Best Actor for Depp, and won for Best Original Score.
The film was the inspiration for the stage musical of the same name in 2012.
The film explores themes of london, england, stroke of fate,
becoming an adult, parent child relationship, faith.
The tone is emotional.